

# **MUHSIN K H**

Dynamic professional with a diverse skill set encompassing public relations, and content creation, offering over 2 years of experience in successfully managing and optimizing operations across multiple industries. Seeking a challenging role in Dubai where I can use my skills to help businesses achieve their marketing goals.

### **6** 0542761638

- muhsin0099@gmail.com
- inkedin.com/in/muhsinkh
- \_\_\_Dubai, UAE

Visa Status: - Resident

Visa Holder, Dubai (UAE)

## **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Arts in English Triple Main

Rajagiri Viswajyothi College 2018 -2021

Actively participated in literary and communication events, enhancing public speaking and critical thinking skills.

Secondary School Certificate Vimalagiri Public School 2016-2018

# **SKILLS**

- Writing
- Blogging
- Copywriting
- Proofreading

## **LANGUAGE**

English

Hindi

Malayalam

Arabic

# **Experience**

Oct 2023- Present Infinio Technology Solutions | Ernakulam,Kerala

### **Senior Content Writer**

Writing and editing compelling articles, posts, and updates to showcase the company's thought leadership and industry expertise.

Collaborating with marketing, sales, and other teams to align content with overall business strategies.

Stayed abreast of industry trends and emerging content formats, implementing innovative approaches to keep content fresh and in line with evolving audience preferences.

Jan 2021- Oct 2023 Neom Building Solutions | Ernakulam,Kerala

### Operations

Collaborated with customers and staff to ensure operational efficiency.

Managed a team of members, achieving a increase in efficiency.

Conducted training sessions for new team members, ensuring seamless integration.

Streamlined inventory management, reducing stock discrepancies

2019 - 2020

NewTech Ply& Boards | Ernakulam, Kerala

#### **Content Creator**

Conducted thorough research to stay up-to-date with industry trends, competitor activities, and emerging topics, ensuring the company's content remained relevant and valuable

.Collaborated with the marketing team to strategize and execute content plans that aligned with the company's branding and marketing objectives.

Monitored content performance using analytics tools, making data-driven adjustments to content strategies to maximize reach and engagement.

# **Certificates Achievements Interests**

Introduction to Digital Journalism(Reuters) (05/2022)

Stanford Introduction

to Food and Health(Stanford

online)(2022)

IELTS ACADEMIC (12/2021) Band Score:7.5

Movies

Reading Travel Writing Sports Art